

ALEKSANDRA TOMALCZYK

CONTACT

667 837 637

ola.tomalczyk@gmail.com

<u>linkedin.com/in/olatomalczyk</u>

github.com/olatomalczyk

EDUCATION

Silesian University of Technology

10/2020 - present

Faculty of Mechanical Engineering

Master's Degree: Automatic Control

and Robotics

Form: Extramural studies

Silesian University of Technology

10/2017 - 09/2020

Faculty of Automatic Control,

Electronics and Computer Science

Engineer's Degree: Automatic Control

and Robotics

Form: Full - time studies

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Basic knowledge of Java, Kotlin and Dart programming languages,
- Basic knowledge of SQL,
- Work with version control system -Git.

LANGUAGES

English: intermediate

HOBBY

- mountainboarding,
- snowboarding,
- off-road.

ABOUT ME

I am an ambitious Automation and Robotization Specialist at Astor Katowice, who knows the basics of programming mobile applications and robots. I feel comfortable working in a team and contacting with clients thanks to excellent communication skills and experience in managing projects. I am not afraid of new challenges, I carry out my daily tasks scrupulously and diligently. I would like to lead my career towards programming mobile applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Astor | Katowice

01/2021 - present

Automation and Robotization Specialist

- Programming and testing of autonomous robots,
- Developing of industrial and autonomous robotic demo applications,
- Providing technical support and assistance related to autonomous robots,
- Providing trainings to customers and colleagues on operating and programming of the autonomous robots,
- Managing and supporting sales projects of the robotic systems,
- Providing sales assistance for robot servicing and inspections,
- Organizing and leading presentations and conferences,
- Preparation of technical documentation.

10/2020 - 01/2021

Internship - Automation and Robotization Junior Specialist

Euvic | Gliwice

07/2020 - 09/2020

Internship - Mobile Apps Developer

- · Developing a comercial mobile application for Android and iOS devices in Flutter technology,
- Cooperation with worldwide customer and engineers,
- Working with Postman and Microsoft Azure DevOps,
- Working in sprint style,
- Creating and developing a project of mobile application for Android in Kotlin language.

COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

- AgilePM Foundation,
- Operating and programming of the EPSON robots in RC+ simulation environment,
- Operating and programming of the Kawasaki robots part 1 course for Users,
- Design and simulation of robotic workstations in the K-Roset,
- E.19 Design and programming of mechatronic devices.

PROJECTS

07/2021 - 08/2021

Mobile application for visualizing weather data from API

10/2019 - 12/2019

Project of smart light system for buldings controlled by a mobile application

2015 - 2016

Conversion of a diesel RC model into an electric one controlled by a mobile application

3rd place in the Regional Olympics of Technical Innovation and Invention

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).